[{"question": " chandler!!! chandler!!!  chandler, i saw what you were doing through the window! chandler, i saw what you were doing to my sister! now get out here!", "answer": "  wow! listen, we had a good run. what was it? four? five months? i mean, that's more than most people have in a lifetime! so, good-bye, take care, bye-bye then!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " what are you doing?!", "answer": " oh, i'm going on the lamb.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " what the hell are doing?!!", "answer": "  hey, what's-what's going on?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " well, i think, i think ross knows about me and monica.", "answer": "  dude! he's right there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": "  i thought you were my best friend, this is my sister! my best friend and my sister! i-i cannot believe this!", "answer": " look, we're not just messing around! i love her. okay, i'm in love with her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": "  my best friend and my sister! i cannot believe this.   you guys probably wanna get some hugs in too, huh? big news!", "answer": " awww, no, it's okay, we've actually known for a while.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " what? what? what?! you guys knew?  you all knew and you didn't tell me?!!", "answer": " well, ross, we were worried about you. we didn't know how you were going to react.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " hey, you know what i just realized? if you guys ever have kids\u009a", "answer": "  whoa-whoa-whoa! we're having kids?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": "  i call godfather!", "answer": " you can't just call godfather. don't you think her brother should be godfather?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " sure, if you cared enough to call it first.", "answer": " guys, you're a few steps ahead of us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " yeah, big zero gravity moon steps.", "answer": " oh! oh, i just thought of the greatest wedding gift to get you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " ooh, i'll go in on that with you! i couldn't think of anything.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  oh, hey katie! everyone, this is katie.", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " so, are you ready to go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " yeah, i just gotta run to the bathroom.", "answer": " oh sure, right back there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " hey, where are we going to lunch?", "answer": " i was thinking chinese food.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " she is so cute! you could fit her right in your little pocket!", "answer": " i don't know. i mean i like her a lot, and she's really nice, but\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " but what?", "answer": "  she keeps punching me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " in that cute, little, sweet way she just did?", "answer": " hey, it's a lot harder than it looks! okay?  she-she-she's hurting me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " i know what you need, you need a bodyguard. hey ross, what is ben doing after preschool?", "answer": " hey listen, come on, joey is having a problem! a little girl is beating him up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey! i brought you some house warming gifts.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " aww.", "answer": " yeah. salt, so your life always has flavor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " huh.", "answer": " bread, so you never go hungry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " ohh.", "answer": " and a scented candle for the bathroom, because well, y'know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " thanks. thanks. and thanks again.", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " welcome to the building. i'm uh, steve sarah; i'm president of the tenants committee.", "answer": " oh hi! ross geller. and this is my friend phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oh hi phoebe.", "answer": " mr. president.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " i came to talk to you about howard.", "answer": " howard?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " yeah, he's the handy man. he's gonna be retiring next week and everyone who lives here is kicking in a 100 bucks as a thank you for all the hard work type of thing.", "answer": " oh that's nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " yeah. so, do you want to give a check? or\u009a", "answer": " oh. uhh\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " no-no, it's not that, it's just\u009a i-i just moved in.", "answer": " well, the guy's worked here for 25 years.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " yes, but i've lived here for 25 minutes.", "answer": " oh, okay, i get it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " no wait, look. look! i'm sorry, it's just i've never even met howard. i-i mean i don't know howard.", "answer": " howard's the handy man!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " yes but too me he's just, man.", "answer": " okay, fine, whatever. welcome to the building.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": "  ugh, can you believe that guy!", "answer": " yeah. i really like his glasses.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " \u009aso then president steve told everyone that i was a cheapskate, and now the whole building hates me! a little kid spit on my knee! y'know what i'm gonna do? i'm gonna throw a party. that's right. for everyone in the building, and i'm gonna sit them down and explain to them, i am not a bad guy. i am not a cheap guy! i'm just a guy who-who stands up for what he believes in. a man with principles.", "answer": "  sounds like a fun party.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " hmm. look, ross, if you want your neighbors to like you, why don't you just pay the hundred bucks? the party's gonna cost you way more than that.", "answer": " it doesn't matter! it's my principles! we're talking about my principles!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " okay, i thought it was about your neighbors liking you.", "answer": " oh, they'll like me. once they come to my awesome par-tay! okay, i gotta run. i gotta go get some nametags.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " and that crazy party animal will be your brother-in-law.", "answer": " very, very funny, but don't say things like that in front of monica. i don't want you putting any ideas in her head.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " umm, chandler, you do realize that those ideas are probably already in monica's head.", "answer": " wh-wh-why?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " well, because she loves you and because you love her.", "answer": " yeah, so, what's that supposed to mean?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " hey, chandler, don't freak out! i'm telling you something you already know! come on, she broke up with richard because he didn't want to have babies. and she's a woman, and she's almost 30, and y'know it's monica.", "answer": " i don't see it that way. okay? because, i see two monicas, the one that was my friend, who lived across the hall, and wanted to have a lot of babies and then the new monica, who i just started to date. now, who's to say what she wants?! i\u0092m right. i'm right. am i right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " no, you're right, you are absolutely right. i mean that makes, that makes everything different.", "answer": " okay. it's not different at all, is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  y'know, breadstick fangs are always funny.", "answer": " no, you make them funny. you're the funny one!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " uhh, look katie, uh listen, we-we need to talk. okay? umm, look i like you. i-i really do, i like you a lot. okay? but sometimes when you, when you playfully punch me like that it-it feels like someone's hitting me with a very tiny but very real bat.", "answer": " aww, like i could hurt you. are you making fun of my size? don't make fun of me because of my size!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " isn't this great?", "answer": " hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " couldn't you just stay like this forever?  chandler! couldn't you just stay here forever?", "answer": " yeah, here, somewhere else, y'know where-where ever.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " are you okay?", "answer": " yeah, i'm cool. casual.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " what-what are you doing?", "answer": " i'm just hanging out. y'know, having fun. y'know with the girl that i'm seeing casually.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " man, i knew it! i knew you were going to do this!!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " get all freaked out because everybody was talking and just joking around about marriage and stuff.", "answer": " well, you do want all that stuff, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " oh and you know what i want!", "answer": " yes! you want babies! you have baby fever!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " i do not have baby fever!", "answer": " oh please, you are obsessed with babies and-and marriage and everything that's related to babies and-and marriage! i've got an idea, why don't we turn down the heat on this pressure cooker?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " have you lost your mind? chandler, this isn't about me! this is about you and all your weird relationship commitment crap!", "answer": " nah-uh! i know you! okay? i know the thoughts that you have in the head--in your head!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " it's gonna be okay, right? i mean she's not gonna leave me? this is, this is fixable. ross and joey: oh yeah, yeah, sure. absolutely.", "answer": " by me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " oh, no!", "answer": " no-no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " well, unless you make some kind of big gesture.", "answer": " yeah, big!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " uh-oh, shht! the misses.", "answer": " gunther, can i get a coffee  to go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " i'm still not done not wanting to talk to you.", "answer": " just tell me what i need to do to make things right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " well, that's what we do. y'know, i-i mess up and then you tell me how to fix it and then i do and then y'know you think i'm all cute again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": "  howard! howard! howard! howard!  howard! howard! howard!  howard! howard! howard! howard! howard!  howard! howard! howard! howard! howard! howard! howard! howard! howard! yay!!", "answer": " phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " oh, hi ross!", "answer": " what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " see ya phoebe! oh and hey, thanks for chipping in!", "answer": " you chipped in?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " yeah, uh-huh, a 100 dollars.", "answer": " phoebe! i can't believe you gave them money! i thought you agreed it was totally unreasonable that they asked me for that money!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " yeah, but they didn't ask me! y'know? this way i'm just y'know, the exotic, generous stranger. that's always fun to be.", "answer": " yeah, but you're making me look bad!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " no i'm not. no! if anything i'm making you look better! they'll see you talking to me and that's--i'm a hit!", "answer": "  oh hey, pheebs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " oh hey, ross. umm, see, i was thinking maybe you two could switch apartments because phoebe's more our kind of people. something to think about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi! wow! you look, you look\u009abig.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " thanks! i've been working out. hey listen, is it obvious that i'm wearing six sweaters?", "answer": " uhhh, yeah. but it's not obvious why.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " well look, i\u0092m breaking up with katie so i had to put on some extra padding. y'know? i mean, if she hits me when she's happy, can you imagine how hard she's gonna hit me when i tell her i'm taking away the joey love?", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " hey! hiya!", "answer": " hey! hey, cute jacket!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " oww!!!! joey, she just kicked me.", "answer": " huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " well? aren't you gonna do something?", "answer": " uhh\u009a.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " you'd better do something, or i'm gonna walk out that door right now! well? are you gonna?", "answer": " nah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  phoebe?", "answer": "  that's what i'm saying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  phoebe? phoebe?", "answer": " ooh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " look, this is a disaster! can't i please just go?", "answer": " no! no! i'm talking you up to people. just give it a little time, all right? relax, get something to eat! okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " so uh, what did you tell them about me?", "answer": " oh, i was telling them about you and emily. y'know, try to get some sympathy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " but somehow you came off as the bad guy.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " yeah, i think i told it wrong. y'know, we should talk about that because i don't totally understand what happened there.", "answer": "  ohh, this cake is really good!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " oh, okay, see? things are looking up already!", "answer": "  oh my god! someone cut howard's cake!  who would do a think like that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " 3-b!", "answer": " oh yeah, aww!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " okay, you got your free food! you ruined everyone's fun! don't you think it's time you went home?!", "answer": " yeah, leave!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " yeah, get out! now!", "answer": " go back to 3-b, 3-b!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " obviously i didn't think they were gonna start throwing things. i just thought if i kept insulting everyone, you would jump in and defend everyone and then you could look like the hero.", "answer": " oh wow, yeah! see, i did not get that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " where's monica?! where is she? i need to talk to her! it's urgent! is she here?", "answer": "  i'm monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " i need to talk to you, it's urgent!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " wait what-wh-wh-what are you doing?!", "answer": "  monica\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " no-no, don't-don't-don't do it!", "answer": " will you marry me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " oh-no. no. no.", "answer": " what a bad idea!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " chandler, why are you doing this?", "answer": " i don't know. but i know i'm not afraid to do this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " chandler.", "answer": " i'm doing this because i'm sorry?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " do you umm, you really think the best reason to get married is because you're sorry?", "answer": " no, the best reason to get married is pregnancy. sorry is pretty much fourth y'know, behind being ready and actually wanting to get married.  will you be my wife?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": "  chandler, umm, i want you to take just a minute and i want you to think about how ridiculous this sounds.", "answer": " yeah, i'm kinda wishing everyone wasn't here right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " honey! do you know that none of that stuff came from me?! i mean i never said i wanted to have babies and get married right now!", "answer": " yeah i know, but i was really confused and then i talked to these guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " who? two divorces and joey?!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " she's right y'know.", "answer": " yeah, but still, cheap shot!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " y'know what? y'know when i said that i want you to deal with this relationship stuff all on your own? well, you're not ready for that.", "answer": " i didn't think i was!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " oh my god, what would have done if i said yes?", "answer": " well i would've been happy because i would've be able to spend the rest of my life with the woman that i love. or, you would've seen a chandler shaped hole in that door.  ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " hey ross, will you pass me that knife?", "answer": " no, i will not!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " oh, it's okay. you don't have to be so mean about", "answer": " you're right, i'm sorry. will you marry me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " aw, and i was gonna ask you to marry me because i forgot to say hello to you last week.", "answer": " oh no wait pheebs, i think for something like that you just ask them to move in with you. but i'm not sure, chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " okay, how long is this going to go on.", "answer": " well i think the length of teasing is directly related to how insane you were so, a long time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " that's not funny.", "answer": " that's not funny at all!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}]